<MealPlanner id="1">
  <users id="2">
    <User id="3">
      <username>user2</username>
      <password>password1</password>
      <goalCalorie>2000</goalCalorie>
      <dietType id="4"/>
      <pastDays id="5"/>
      <currentDay id="6">
        <date id="7">1899-12-31</date>
        <calorieCount>0</calorieCount>
        <meals id="8"/>
      </currentDay>
      <ownedIngredients id="9"/>
      <savedRecipes id="10"/>
    </User>
  </users>
  <recipes id="11">
    <Recipe id="12">
      <calorieCountPerServing>150</calorieCountPerServing>
      <name>marsBar</name>
      <dietType id="13"/>
      <ingredients id="14"/>
      <steps></steps>
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="15">
      <calorieCountPerServing>600</calorieCountPerServing>
      <name>Smoked salmon &amp; spinach gratin</name>
      <dietType id="16"/>
      <ingredients id="17">
        <mealPlanner.model.Ingredient id="18">
          <name>spinach</name>
        </mealPlanner.model.Ingredient>
        <mealPlanner.model.Ingredient id="19">
          <name>butter</name>
        </mealPlanner.model.Ingredient>
        <mealPlanner.model.Ingredient id="20">
          <name>salmon fillets</name>
        </mealPlanner.model.Ingredient>
        <mealPlanner.model.Ingredient id="21">
          <name>double cream</name>
        </mealPlanner.model.Ingredient>
      </ingredients>
      <steps>Put the spinach in a really big saucepan (or two saucepans) and add a few tablespoons of water. Cover, set over a medium heat and cook for about 5-8 mins, turning the spinach over every so often, until wilted. Tip it into a colander to drain and allow it to cool (spread it out on a plate to cool it quicker). Take big handfuls of it in your fists and squeeze out the excess water. It?s really important that you do this, otherwise the water will leach out and make the cream watery and green.-----Chop the spinach. Melt the butter in a saucepan and gently toss the spinach in it. Season with pepper and a tiny bit of salt (there?s so much salt in the salmon). Heat the oven to 160C/140C fan/gas 3. Lay the spinach in the bottom of a gratin dish (about 30cm x 20cm), then arrange the salmon fillets on top.Heat the double cream in a small pan, then pour it all over the salmon and spinach. Bake for 35 mins, or until the top is golden and the cream is bubbling.</steps>
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="22">
      <calorieCountPerServing>500</calorieCountPerServing>
      <name>Pesto Kale Pasta</name>
      <dietType id="23">
        <mealPlanner.model.DietType id="24">
          <type>Vegeterian</type>
        </mealPlanner.model.DietType>
      </dietType>
      <ingredients id="25">
        <mealPlanner.model.Ingredient id="26">
          <name>pesto</name>
        </mealPlanner.model.Ingredient>
        <mealPlanner.model.Ingredient id="27">
          <name>cream cheese</name>
        </mealPlanner.model.Ingredient>
        <mealPlanner.model.Ingredient id="28">
          <name>rapeseed oil</name>
        </mealPlanner.model.Ingredient>
        <mealPlanner.model.Ingredient id="29">
          <name>red Onion</name>
        </mealPlanner.model.Ingredient>
        <mealPlanner.model.Ingredient id="30">
          <name>kale</name>
        </mealPlanner.model.Ingredient>
        <mealPlanner.model.Ingredient id="31">
          <name>pasta</name>
        </mealPlanner.model.Ingredient>
      </ingredients>
      <steps>Heat the oil in a large pan over a medium heat. Fry the onions for 10 mins until softened and beginning to caramelise. Add the kale and 100ml water, then cover and cook for 5 mins more, or until the kale has wilted.----Cook the pasta following pack instructions. Drain, reserving a little of the cooking water. Toss the pasta with the onion mixture, cream cheese and pesto, adding a splash of the reserved cooking water to loosen, if needed. Season.</steps>
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="32">
      <calorieCountPerServing>300</calorieCountPerServing>
      <name>Miso mushroom &amp; tofu noodle soup</name>
      <dietType id="33"/>
      <ingredients id="34">
        <mealPlanner.model.Ingredient id="35">
          <name>mushrooms</name>
        </mealPlanner.model.Ingredient>
        <mealPlanner.model.Ingredient id="36">
          <name>brown rice</name>
        </mealPlanner.model.Ingredient>
        <mealPlanner.model.Ingredient id="37">
          <name>noodles</name>
        </mealPlanner.model.Ingredient>
        <mealPlanner.model.Ingredient reference="29"/>
        <mealPlanner.model.Ingredient reference="28"/>
      </ingredients>
      <steps>Heat half the oil in a frying pan over a medium heat. Add the mushrooms and fry for 5-6 mins, or until golden. Transfer to a bowl using a slotted spoon and set aside. Add the remaining oil to the pan and fry the tofu for 3-4 mins, or until evenly golden.------Mix the miso paste with 325ml boiling water in a jug. Cook the noodles following pack instructions, then drain and transfer to a bowl. Top with the mushrooms and tofu, then pour over the miso broth. Scatter over the spring onions just before serving.</steps>
    </Recipe>
  </recipes>
</MealPlanner>